#### Contact

+97235515375 (Home) tbaror@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tal-baror-0371986 (LinkedIn) www.dalet.com (Company)

### Top Skills

**VMware** 

Servers

Virtualization

#### Languages

English (Full Professional)
French (Full Professional)
Hebrew (Native or Bilingual)

#### Certifications

**MCSE** 

**CCSA** 

Network+

Security+

# Tal Bar-Or

Head of IT at Dalet Digital Media Systems

# Summary

I am A Very experienced Corporate Infrastructures & Network/ Systems Manager in multi-national companies, With more than 20 years of experience and a mix of in-depth HANDS-ON Technical work As well as strong Business/Financial orientation & IT Team management, Procurement, Subcontractors Management, Work plans& Reporting to senior management.

- Strong Business/Financial orientation: Cost saving, "Do More With Less", IT Management Processes (BSM/ITIL) and so forth. Very experienced with Managing IT at low costs and small budgets!
- Extensive and deep Technical knowledge & skills at Microsoft Technologies & VMware Technologies: Windows Server 2000/2003/2008, Windows 2000/2003/2008, Virtual Infrastructure 3.5, VMware VDI/SRM/Lab Manager, Checkpoint Firewall-1,Video Servers, Information Security IPS/IDS, Cisco/HP/3COM/DELL/IBM equipment and many more.
- High Ability to delve into new fields, Technologies and & implement new technologies-in terms of speed and depth.
- Diligent, Team & project leader
- High ability to interact, present and execute plans for senior management, Discrete and trustworthy given the sensitive position.
   My extensive IT Management Experience & Skills Both Professional And managemental, Will be an asset to any company.

Specialties: Microsoft Servers 2kx, SQL Server, VMware Sphere,Xen,Ovirt and complementary products: SRM/VDI, Lab Manager

Linux, CheckPoint, Isilon, NetApp, DDN,Freenas,Gluster,ITIL/BSM,HP Procurve/Cisco/Dell, Network/IT Systems Design & Architecture, Purchasing, Budget planning, Work Plans, Project Managent, System Administration & Ongoing Administration, IT Team Management, DataCenter Management

# Experience

## Dalet Head of IT/Support Engineer June 2004 - Present Israel

Dalet Digital Media Systems Head of IT June 2004 - Present

Dalet System aministrator 2004 - Present

Citigroup System/Network Administrator June 2000 - June 2004 (4 years 1 month) Paris Area, France

System/Network Administrator Paris Citigroup

Citigroup System aministrator 2000 - 2004 (5 years) Paris Area, France

#### **GAN**

System/Network Administrator December 1999 - May 2000 (6 months) Paris Area, France

Taldor System/Network Administrator March 1996 - November 1999 (3 years 9 months)

# Education

Self-Taught
MCSE 2003, System Engineering · (2006 - 2006)

Self-Taught
ComptiA Network+, System Engineering · (2003 - 2003)

# Self-Taught

CCSA (Check Point), Information Security · (2003 - 2003)

## Self-Taught

MCSE 2000, System Engineering · (2002 - 2003)

## Self-Taught

MCP's NT 4, System Engineering · (1998 - 1998)